Guide to the Walter L. Pforzheimer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- April 2003 Acquisition, 85.71; (89 boxes) + 4 broadside folders, 2 cold storage packages, 5 framed art storage items, 3 object storage items
  - Military Intelligence and Personal Papers
    - 4 videocassettes, 20 audiocassettes (Box 111)
      Includes interviews with Pforzheimer, conference presentations by Pforzheimer
    - Stamp collection (Box 112)
    - Stamp collection (Box 113)
    - Photographs, negatives (Box 114)
    - Photographs, negatives (Box 115)
    - Photographs, negatives (Box 116)
    - Photographs, negatives (Box 117)
  - Oversize
    - Prints, photographs (Box 118 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 119 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 120 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 121 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 122 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 123 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 124 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 125 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 126 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 127 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 128 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards (Box 129 Oversize)
    - Photograph albums (Box 130 Oversize)
    - Rolled items (Box 131 Oversize)
    - Photographs, prints, awards, board game (Box 132 Oversize)
    - Framed items (Box 133 Oversize)
    - Framed items (Box 134 Oversize)
    - Framed items (Box 135 Oversize)
    - Framed items (Box 136 Oversize)
    - Matted photographs, map (Box 137 Broadside folder)
    - Framed photograph (Box 138 Broadside folder)
    - Framed photograph (Box 139 Broadside folder)
    - Framed print (Box 140 Broadside folder)
  - Restricted Fragile
    Box 160 (computer disks): Reference copies are available. For further information consult Access Services.
    - "Church in Bavaria." oil painting by Dwight D. Eisenhower (Box 141 Framed art storage)
    - "President George Washington." oil painting by Dwight D. Eisenhower (Box 142 Framed art storage)
    - Unidentified. oil painting (Box 143 Framed art storage)
    - Unidentified. oil painting (Box 143a Framed art storage)
    - "Abraham Lincoln." print (Box 144 Framed art storage)
    - Fire bucket (Box 145)
    - Fire bucket, objects (Box 146)
    - Textiles, binocular case (Box 147)
    - Objects (Box 148)
    - Objects (Box 149)
    - Tobacco pipe (Box 150)
    - Tobacco pipes (Box 151 Object storage)
    - Objects (Box 152)
    - Framed mirror (Box 153 Object storage)
    - Glass stereographs (Box 154)
    - Glass stereographs (Box 155)
    - Glass stereographs (Box 156)
    - Glass stereographs (Box 157)
    - Glass stereographs (Box 158)
    - Louis XV chandelier (Box 159 Object storage)
    - Computer disks, (4 5.5 inch disks) (Box 160)
    - NASA color photographs, (3 albums) (Box 161 Cold storage)
    - Family photographs. nitrate negatives, circa 1910s-1930s (Box 162 Cold storage)
- January 2005 Acquisition, 0.63; (2 boxes) + 1 portfolio
  Boxes and folders are unarranged.
  Contains a small amount of materials similar to other acquisition groupings, including papers relating to Pforzheimer's intelligence career, and computer disks.
  - Military Intelligence and Personal Papers
    - Papers (Box 163)
  - Oversize
    - Papers (Box 164)
  - Restricted Fragile
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies are available. For further information consult Access Services.
    - Computer disks, (2 5.5 inch disks) (Box 165)
- Unidentified Acquisitions, 0.29; (2 boxes)
  Folders are unarranged.
  Contains historical manuscripts and related materials collected by Pforzheimer concerning the history of military intelligence. These materials are part of one or more of the acquisitions listed above, but were not included in preliminary processing.
  - Historical Manuscripts
    - Manuscripts removed from books, 4 (Box 166)
    - Charles I, King of England (Box 166)
    - Unidentified, 4 (Box 166)
    - Related materials (Box 166)
  - Oversize
    - Louis XIV, King of France, 2 (Box 167)
    - Turenne, Henri de La Tour d'Auvergne, vicomte de (Box 167)